https://www.discountfavors.com/privacy.html

BAGS &AMP TOTESPROMOTIONS
BackpacksBank BagsBusiness BagsCoolersDuffel BagsLuggage TagsPaper BagsPlastic BagsTote BagsTravel BagsNone
Desktop & Office
DESKTOP &AMP OFFICEPROMOTIONS
CalculatorsClipsClocksDesk AccessoriesLetter OpenersMagnetsPicture FramesRadiosRulersStress BallsWatchesNone
Drinkware
DRINKWAREPROMOTIONS
Ceramic MugsCoastersDisposable CupsGlasswareCan CoolersNapkinsPlastic Beer SteinsPlatesSports BottlesStadium CupsTravel MugsNone
STATIONERYPROMOTIONS
BindersCalendarsCard HoldersCubes Pads FlagsDocument HoldersFoldersJottersNotebooksPortfoliosSticky NotesNone
Privacy and Security
The DiscountFavors.com ("DiscountFavors") Web Site ("Web Site") is a wholly-owned subsidiary of Handy Advertising, LLC and the sole owner of the information collected on the Web Site. We collect personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web Site. DiscountFavors is committed to protecting the privacy of users of this Web Site and the information you provide.
Orders
If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.
Communications from the Site & Special Offers, Updates and Newsletters
We will occasionally send out information on products, services, special deals, and promotions. You can sign up for these emails from us on every page of the site. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications.
Service-related Announcements
We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
We do not share aggregated demographic information about our user base. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.
Personally identifiable information
We share personally identifiable information with selected third parties. This information is only provided to enable fulfillment and shipping of products and services you have purchased from DiscountFavors.
Other Information
We share your mailing address with some carefully screened vendors whom we feel may provide products and services that will be of benefit to you. If you do not want us to share your mailing information please email us at sales@discountfavors.com, or call us at 1-800-939-1980 and we will opt you out of these offers. At no time does DiscountFavors release your email address or telephone number.
Agents
We use outside suppliers and shipping companies to fulfill orders. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.
Service Providers
We use other third parties to provide software and hosting services for our site. We do not share any personally identifiable information with these service providers.
Legal Disclaimer
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web Site.
Choice/Opt-out
We provide you the opportunity to "opt-out" of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference.
If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by indicating such on the 'Email Sign up' page.
Log Files
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data.
We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.
Cookies
Cookies are files Web browsers place on a computer's hard drive. They are used to help us authenticate clients and provide time saving shortcuts and preferences. DiscountFavors uses a persistent encrypted cookie, if the client requests, to save and retrieve individual authentication information as well as other per-client device preferences. When a visitor follows a link to the DiscountFavors Web Site from an affiliate or promotion, DiscountFavors stores information about that affiliate or promotion in a session cookie. Acceptance of these cookies is optional. DiscountFavors issues a mandatory session cookie to each user of the Services only to record encrypted authentication information for the duration of a specific session. If you reject this cookie, access to and usage of the Services will be denied.
Clear Gifs (web Beacons/web Bugs)
We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. web Beacons/web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the on-line movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personally identifiable information.
We may use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see "Choice/Opt-out."
Links to Other Sites
This Web Site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by DiscountFavors. Please be aware that we, DiscountFavors, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web Site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web Site.
Access to Personally Identifiable Information
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page, by emailing our Customer Support at: sales@discountfavors.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.
SECURITY
The security of your personal information, as well as PCI compliance, is very important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as passwords, phone numbers or address) on our Web Site forms, we encrypt that information using Secure Socket Layer technology (SSL). Look for the address "https://www.discountfavors.com" in the navigation bar of your favorite browser AS WELL AS the padlock symbol. DO NOT ENTER ANY INFORMATION ABSCENT THESE SECURITY FEATURES.
DiscountFavors uses the latest, up-to-date security features. Occasionally, false positives are triggered. If you not a malicious actor and are redirected to our security page, please call the 1-800 number for assistance.
Credit Card Data
DiscountFavors DOES NOT COLLECT or pass credit card data through our Web Site, web server ("Server") OR STORE credit card data in our database ("dB") or accounting applications. All data is entered into a secure, PCI compliant web form hosted by PayPal (the "Processor"). DiscountFavors seamlessly redirects you, the customer, to the Processor's secure, PCI compliant web form for data entry and processing. You are returned to DiscountFavors upon completion, along with a non-credit card data (name, address, and phone number) "packet" required to process your order.
We follow universally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us (an SSL certificate). However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its security and make no claim to that effect. If you have any questions about security on our Web Site, you can send email to us: sales@discountfavors.com
Business Transitions
In the event DiscountFavors goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Web Site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.
Third Party Sites
The DiscountFavors Web Site and on-line applications contain links to other web sites. DiscountFavors is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web sites. Customers and visitors must check the policy statement of these others web sites to understand their policies. Customers and visitors who access a linked site may be disclosing their private information. It is your responsibility to keep such information private and confidential.
Changes in this Privacy Statement
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
Contact Information
Please feel free to contact us at:DiscountFavors.com7801 NW 67th St.Miami, FL 33166
Facebook
Twitter
YouTube
Google+
TOP CATEGORIES
Bags & Totes
Clearance
Desktop & Office
Email Deal Alerts
Enter your email address to receive promotions and special offers from Discount Favors.
Safe & Secure
You can shop with confidence here at Discount Favors, knowing that your private information is safe with us. We understand your concerns about privacy and security, and work daily to insure that your order is processed with the upmost protection. Verisign Insured, you can rest assured that your credit card information is entered and processed safely. We guarantee that we will never share, rent, or sell any of your private information. When you shop with Discount Favors, you shop protected!
Factory Direct Pricing
There's no need to shop around: we guarantee the best pricing in the country. Give us a try and start saving today.
FREE Virtual Proof
We provide FREE art services with unlimited revisions. We provide a FREE proof review of your product imprint which you have to approve before we begin production.
Accepted Payment Methods
Not responsible for printing or typographical errors. Prices, policies, and availability are subject to change without notice.
© 2020 DiscountFavors.com — Promotional Products — All Rights Reserved.
